[Music]
there's something special about a snowy
day
when the world turns varying shades of
blue gray and white
with hints of color dappled among the
pines
the snow i find is a gentle entity
hushing sounds and creating a space that
feels
[Music]
celestial
luke and i love to spend time by the
river and in the winter it's
particularly
stunning the ripples of snow covering
the rocky banks contrasted with the icy
darkness of the water
there's something innately calming about
the view
i first met luke two summers ago when i
had first moved here
as someone who is happily single i
wasn't too keen on the idea to put it
mildly it's very liberating to be your
own best friend
because relationships are no longer a
desperate necessity
instead they are a rich compliment to
your pre-existing happiness
[Music]
my relationship is a way of grounding me
a gentle reminder that cultivating
friendships
no matter what form they take can
challenge you in the best way
and make you a better person because of
it interactions aren't always easy
love is a feeling but also at times a
choice
and the same goes for living i don't
always feel happy because
feelings come and go but there's nothing
i can do about that
i can choose to be simply content and
for me
that's led to a deeper fulfillment that
is unshaken by more fleeting emotions
[Music]
our mutual commitment has made us able
to enjoy the good times and occasional
struggles with grace
it also helps that we have very similar
energy and do not feel pressure to
constantly
do new things instead we simply enjoy
each other's company
as we go about our daily tasks
[Music]
as you can see luke is also an artist
and i invited him over so that he could
share a bit of his process with you
while i worked on some salto ornaments
that i'm making for my students to paint
[Music]
art comes in many forms complex
and simple and each has its own worth
i encourage you to find a creative
outlet whatever it may be
even if your projects don't turn out
exactly how you wish
don't let yourself judge it too harshly
when we compare our own creations with
those of another
we devalue the story of the item we made
it may not be perfect but it is our own
i think that goes for living as well
our imperfections our stylistic details
and our personal decisions creative
license
living is an art make it your own and
don't compare your story with that of
[Music]
another
she's
[Music]
as two creative spirits we have
connected over our shared love
of beautiful things luke enjoys to hike
up mountains searching for crystals
and his interest in gemstones led him to
begin wire weaving
which is an art form i had never heard
about until i met him
but it is absolutely stunning
[Music]
he is a wonderful example of what
patience and practice can achieve
and how creativity blossoms when you let
go of your self-consciousness
i admire him greatly for that and take
his example every day
[Music]
you